Guide to Chris Felver's Group Surrounding Allen Ginsberg, 1980 - 1993
Department of Special Collections
Chris Felver's Group Surrounding Allen Ginsberg,
1980 - 1993
Special Collections MSS Photo 437
Felver, Chris
.25 linear ft.
Stanford University. Libraries. Dept. of Special Collections and University Archives.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
None.
Provenance
Purchased, 1999.
Abstract
Chris Felver's Group surrounding Allen Ginsberg is a collection of 30 black and white photographs arranged in a six by five photograph grid with a photograph of Allen Ginsberg at its center. The photos were taken by Felver from 1980 to 1993.
Container List
- Abbie Hoffman 1982, 1 photograph: b. & w.; 154 x 101 mm. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Grid location: A1
- Anne Waldman 1981, 1 photograph: b. & w.; 154 x 101 mm. (Box 1, Folder 2)
  Grid location: A2
- William S. Burroughs 1981, 1 photograph: b. & w.; 154 x 101 mm. (Box 1, Folder 3)
  Grid location: A3
- Philip LaMantia 1984, 1 photograph: b. & w.; 154 x 101 mm. (Box 1, Folder 4)
  Grid location: A4
- Gary Snyder 1993, 1 photograph: b. & w.; 154 x 101 mm. (Box 1, Folder 5)
  Grid location: A5
- Jack Micheline 1981, 1 photograph: b. & w.; 154 x 101 mm. (Box 1, Folder 6)
  Grid location: B1
- Carl Solomon 1982, 1 photograph: b. & w.; 154 x 101 mm. (Box 1, Folder 7)
  Grid location: B2
- Herbert Huncke 1984, 1 photograph: b. & w.; 154 x 101 mm. (Box 1, Folder 8)
  Grid location: B3
- Robert Creeley 1983, 1 photograph: b. & w.; 154 x 101 mm. (Box 1, Folder 9)
  Grid location: B4
- Tuli Kupferberg 1984, 1 photograph: b. & w.; 154 x 101 mm. (Box 1, Folder 10)
  Grid location: B5
- Diane DiPrima 1981, 1 photograph: b. & w.; 154 x 101 mm. (Box 1, Folder 11)
  Grid location: C1
- Peter Orlovsky 1981, 1 photograph: b. & w.; 154 x 101 mm. (Box 1, Folder 12)
  Grid location: C2
- Allen Ginsberg 1981, 1 photograph: b. & w.; 154 x 101 mm. (Box 1, Folder 13)
  Grid location: C3
- Philip Whalen 1982, 1 photograph: b. & w.; 154 x 101 mm. (Box 1, Folder 14)
  Grid location: C4
- Ted Joans 1984, 1 photograph: b. & w.; 154 x 101 mm. (Box 1, Folder 15)
  Grid location: C5
- Gregory Corso 1981, 1 photograph: b. & w.; 154 x 101 mm. (Box 1, Folder 16)
  Grid location: D1
- Bobbie Louise Hawkins 1982, 1 photograph: b. & w.; 154 x 101 mm. (Box 1, Folder 17)
  Grid location: D2
- Bob Kaufman 1984, 1 photograph: b. & w.; 154 x 101 mm. (Box 1, Folder 18)
  Grid location: D3
- Ed Saunders 1984, 1 photograph: b. & w.; 154 x 101 mm. (Box 1, Folder 19)
  Grid location: D4
- Seymour Krim 1982, 1 photograph: b. & w.; 154 x 101 mm. (Box 1, Folder 20)
  Grid location: D5
- Michael McClure 1981, 1 photograph: b. & w.; 154 x 101 mm. (Box 1, Folder 21)
  Grid location: E1
- Lawrence Ferlinghetti 1980, 1 photograph: b. & w.; 154 x 101 mm. (Box 1, Folder 22)
  Grid location: E2
- Timothy Leary 1982, 1 photograph: b. & w.; 154 x 101 mm. (Box 1, Folder 23)
  Grid location: E3
- Amiri Baraka 1984, 1 photograph: b. & w.; 154 x 101 mm. (Box 1, Folder 24)
  Grid location: E4
- Harold Norse 1982, 1 photograph: b. & w.; 154 x 101 mm. (Box 1, Folder 25)
  Grid location: E5
- Cecil Taylor 1985, 1 photograph: b. & w.; 154 x 101 mm. (Box 1, Folder 26)
  Grid location: F1
- John Weiners 1985, 1 photograph: b. & w.; 154 x 101 mm. (Box 1, Folder 27)
  Grid location: F2
- Howard Hart 1983, 1 photograph: b. & w.; 154 x 101 mm. (Box 1, Folder 28)
  Grid location: F3
- Ken Kesey 1982, 1 photograph: b. & w.; 154 x 101 mm. (Box 1, Folder 29)
  Grid location: F4
- JoAnne Kyger 1982, 1 photograph: b. & w.; 154 x 101 mm. (Box 1, Folder 30)
  Grid location: F5